{
    "id": "e8edca2def7f42968a6d922b7ba7d214",
    "title": "Gap Fills Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I want to know …………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "what are you doing there",
                "what you are doing there"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "If he had asked me ......................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "I will help him",
                "I would help him",
                "I would have helped him"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "She would have come .....................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "if you invite her",
                "if you invited her",
                "if you had invited her"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "We are looking forward to ………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "see you",
                "seeing you"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "No sooner did the teacher enter the class ..................... .",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "when the students stopped talking",
                "than the students stopped talking"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Would you mind .....................?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to move a bit",
                "moving a bit"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Unless you study well, …………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "you will pass",
                "you will not pass"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He worked ………………… that his health broke down.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "very hard",
                "too hard",
                "so hard"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "She is very fond …………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with her grandchildren",
                "of her grandchildren",
                "to her grandchildren"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She is very proud ......................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with her achievements",
                "about her achievements",
                "of her achievements"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        }
    ]
}